I kept this old recipe card for twenty years.
I kept this old recipe
card for twenty years.
The card is stained with oil and faded at the edges. Her handwriting is barely legible now.
The card is stained with oil and faded at the
edges. Her handwriting is barely legible now.
But every time I hold it, I can smell her kitchen.
But every time I hold it,
I can smell her kitchen.
The sound of the radio playing boleros. The way she hummed while she stirred.
The sound of the radio playing boleros.
The way she hummed while she stirred.
She passed when I was twelve. I never got to tell her that her food was the only thing that made Sundays feel like home.
She passed when I was twelve. I never got to tell her that
her food was the only thing that made Sundays feel like home.